<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Statistical analysis on Zhi Yang</title>
    <link>/tags/statistical-analysis/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Statistical analysis on Zhi Yang</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/statistical-analysis/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How difficult it is to get into the top universities in China</title>
      <link>/post/gaokao/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/gaokao/</guid>
      <description>BackgroundIn June of 2019, over 10 millions students took the gaokao, the college entrace exam in China. This exam varies by province to province, so it is the admission rate to the top universities (Beijing/Tsinghua University). I often get asked how difficult to get into those two schools in China. I hope this data visualization will help you understand the admission rates of the top universities across different provinces in China by using the data in 2017.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yes! I tried the new poster style at a conference</title>
      <link>/post/poster/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/poster/</guid>
      <description>Background I worked for Jessica Barrington-Trimis (@Doctor_BT) on a project to look into the effect of e-cigarette use on cigarette use among adolescents. After we submitted the manuscript, Jessica suggested me presenting the results at the upcoming 2019 Meeting – College on Problems of Drug Dependence, San Antonio, TX. Meanwhile, she sent me a video link about transforming the current poster style. After watching it, I was totally down to get the new poster rolling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E-cigarette product characteristics</title>
      <link>/talk/cpdd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2019 18:30:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talk/cpdd/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E-cigarette use among adolescents</title>
      <link>/project/ecig/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/ecig/</guid>
      <description>This project is focused on studying e-cigarette Product Characteristics and Frequency of Smoking Among Young Adults. Previous research suggests that e-cigarette use is associated with cigarette initiation, including the frequency and heaviness of cigarette smoking. The goal of this research is to examine the impact of specific e-cigarette characteristics on cigarette smoking frequency. What we did is to use advanced counts model to model the association between the e-cigarette exposures and the outcome, the number of cigarette use in the past 30 days.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Regular Latin dancing and health education may improve cognition of late middle-aged and older Latinos</title>
      <link>/publication/dance/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2017 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/dance/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Colorectal cancer study</title>
      <link>/project/cancer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/cancer/</guid>
      <description>During my doctoral training, most of my research is focused on developing novel statistical methods for genomics data, specifically, cancer development and tumor growth. This project has enlighted me to work on several interesting perspectives of it, including hierarchical topics model, clustering, and interactive interface. Thanks to my advisors Kimberly Siegmund, and committe member Paul Marjoram and Darryl Shibata.
Motivations Topic models have been widely applied to extract topics from various range of documents or collections of texts, i.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>