<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>admin on Zhi Yang</title>
    <link>/authors/admin/</link>
    <description>Recent content in admin on Zhi Yang</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/authors/admin/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Display Jupyter Notebooks with Academic</title>
      <link>/post/jupyter/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/jupyter/</guid>
      <description>from IPython.core.display import Image Image(&#39;https://www.python.org/static/community_logos/python-logo-master-v3-TM-flattened.png&#39;)  print(&amp;quot;Welcome to Academic!&amp;quot;)  Welcome to Academic!  Install Python and Jupyter Install Anaconda which includes Python 3 and Jupyter notebook.
Otherwise, for advanced users, install Jupyter notebook with pip3 install jupyter.
Create a new blog post as usual Run the following commands in your Terminal, substituting &amp;lt;MY_WEBSITE_FOLDER&amp;gt; and my-post with the file path to your Academic website folder and a name for your blog post (without spaces), respectively:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn how to make a header with R hex-stickers for LinkedIn and Twitter</title>
      <link>/post/hexwall/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/hexwall/</guid>
      <description>Background Nowadays, peoples use LinkedIn and Twitter to look for opportunities and network with others. Except for gaining more skills and doing projects to boost your profile, there is another way to make your profile more professional: finding the right header. No one will argue with the fact that the header picture helps with creating the first impression for recruiters and your future employers. To begin with creating a profile, it might take forever for you to pick their favorite picture as the header but still keep professional.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Academic: the website designer for Hugo</title>
      <link>/post/getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/getting-started/</guid>
      <description>Academic makes it easy to create a beautiful website for free using Markdown. Customize anything on your site with widgets, themes, and language packs.
Follow our easy step by step guide to learn how to build your own free website with Academic. Check out the personal demo or the business demo of what you&amp;rsquo;ll get in less than 10 minutes.
 View the documentation Ask a question Request a feature or report a bug Updating?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/author/admin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/author/admin/</guid>
      <description>Zhi Yang is a PhD candidate in biostatistics at the University of Southern California. She has been providing statistical support to a wide range of research teams in both academia and industry to answer real-life problems, including e-cigarette policy, Alzheimer&amp;rsquo;s prevention, drug marketing strategy, free-roaming dogs vaccination strategy in Africa, colorectal cancer development, e-cigarette use among adolescents and etc. She has over six years&amp;rsquo; programming experiences in R, SQL, SAS, and Stata.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>