<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>admin on Zhi Yang</title>
    <link>/authors/admin/</link>
    <description>Recent content in admin on Zhi Yang</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/authors/admin/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How difficult it is to get into the top universities in China</title>
      <link>/post/gaokao/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/gaokao/</guid>
      <description>BackgroundIn June of 2019, over 10 millions students took the gaokao, the college entrace exam in China. This exam varies by province to province, so it is the admission rate to the top universities (Beijing/Tsinghua University). I often get asked how difficult to get into those two schools in China. I hope this data visualization will help you understand the admission rates of the top universities across different provinces in China by using the data in 2017.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yes! I tried the new poster style at a conference</title>
      <link>/post/poster/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/poster/</guid>
      <description>Background I worked for Jessica Barrington-Trimis (@Doctor_BT) on a project to look into the effect of e-cigarette use on cigarette use among adolescents. After we submitted the manuscript, Jessica suggested me presenting the results at the upcoming 2019 Meeting – College on Problems of Drug Dependence, San Antonio, TX. Meanwhile, she sent me a video link about transforming the current poster style. After watching it, I was totally down to get the new poster rolling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My experience with using H2O Flow</title>
      <link>/post/h2o/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/h2o/</guid>
      <description>Background I came across H2O several times in the past couple of years but I didn&amp;rsquo;t get a chance to try it out by myself. Until very recently, I went to the SatRday Los Angeles conference 2019 at UCLA this year where Erin LeDell (@ledell) gave a keynote talk on scalable automatic machine learning with H2O. The elegant way she has navigated the model building process has fascinated me. Most importantly, H2O also has a very nice and friendly interface called H2O flow to users to quickly familiarize themselves with this tool.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to prepare for data scientist interviews with an eCommerce company</title>
      <link>/post/ecommerce/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/ecommerce/</guid>
      <description>Background I didn&amp;rsquo;t come up with any of those original contents. Here is just a summary of what I&amp;rsquo;ve summarized by learning from reading others&amp;rsquo; insights in how data science contribute to the growth of eCommerce companies and what challenges we are faced with while working as a data scientist at the company.
5 Data Science Projects Every E-commerce Company Should Do In this article, the author talked about five important DS projects that should be undergoing at every eCommerce company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What I learned from practicing interviews on Pramp.com</title>
      <link>/post/pramp/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/pramp/</guid>
      <description>I came across this website to prepare for people to ace interviews for data scientist jobs in the industry. It was mentioned and recommended in the post written by Daniel Miller, a data scientist at Microsoft. I was a little suspicious at the first beginning because I don&amp;rsquo;t think there will be any free services in helping people with improving their interview skills. Normally, we get help from the school Careers Center.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Display Jupyter Notebooks with Academic</title>
      <link>/post/jupyter/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/jupyter/</guid>
      <description>from IPython.core.display import Image Image(&#39;https://www.python.org/static/community_logos/python-logo-master-v3-TM-flattened.png&#39;)  print(&amp;quot;Welcome to Academic!&amp;quot;)  Welcome to Academic!  Install Python and Jupyter Install Anaconda which includes Python 3 and Jupyter notebook.
Otherwise, for advanced users, install Jupyter notebook with pip3 install jupyter.
Create a new blog post as usual Run the following commands in your Terminal, substituting &amp;lt;MY_WEBSITE_FOLDER&amp;gt; and my-post with the file path to your Academic website folder and a name for your blog post (without spaces), respectively:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn how to make a header with R hex-stickers for LinkedIn and Twitter</title>
      <link>/post/hexwall/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/hexwall/</guid>
      <description>Background Nowadays, peoples use LinkedIn and Twitter to look for opportunities and network with others. Except for gaining more skills and doing projects to boost your profile, there is another way to make your profile more professional: finding the right header. No one will argue with the fact that the header picture helps with creating the first impression for recruiters and your future employers. To begin with creating a profile, it might take forever for you to pick their favorite picture as the header but still keep professional.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Academic: the website designer for Hugo</title>
      <link>/post/getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/getting-started/</guid>
      <description>Academic makes it easy to create a beautiful website for free using Markdown. Customize anything on your site with widgets, themes, and language packs.
Follow our easy step by step guide to learn how to build your own free website with Academic. Check out the personal demo or the business demo of what you&amp;rsquo;ll get in less than 10 minutes.
 View the documentation Ask a question Request a feature or report a bug Updating?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/author/admin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/author/admin/</guid>
      <description>Zhi Yang is a PhD candidate in biostatistics at the University of Southern California. She has been providing statistical support to a wide range of research teams in both academia and industry to answer real-life problems, including e-cigarette policy, Alzheimer&amp;rsquo;s prevention, drug marketing strategy, free-roaming dogs vaccination strategy in Africa, colorectal cancer development, e-cigarette use among adolescents and etc. She has over six years&amp;rsquo; programming experiences in R, SQL, SAS, and Stata.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>