<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Zhi Yang on Zhi Yang</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Zhi Yang on Zhi Yang</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2019 18:30:00 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>E-cigarette product characteristics</title>
      <link>/talk/cpdd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2019 18:30:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talk/cpdd/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;poster.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Extracting topics from cancer patients&#39; mutational profiles</title>
      <link>/talk/ml4all/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 14:30:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talk/ml4all/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My experience with using H2O Flow</title>
      <link>/post/h2o/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/h2o/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;background&#34;&gt;Background&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I came across H&lt;sub&gt;2&lt;/sub&gt;O several times in the past couple of years but I didn&amp;rsquo;t get a chance to try it out by myself. Until very recently, I went to the &lt;a href=&#34;https://losangeles2019.satrdays.org/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;SatRday Los Angeles conference 2019&lt;/a&gt; at UCLA this year where Erin LeDell (&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/ledell&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;@ledell&lt;/a&gt;) gave a keynote talk on &lt;a href=&#34;https://youtu.be/A3EmOgpoG60&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;scalable automatic machine learning with H2O&lt;/a&gt;. The elegant way she has navigated the model building process has fascinated me. Most importantly, H&lt;sub&gt;2&lt;/sub&gt;O also has a very nice and friendly interface called H&lt;sub&gt;2&lt;/sub&gt;O flow to users to quickly familiarize themselves with this tool. Here is a more detailed and official &lt;a href=&#34;http://docs.h2o.ai/h2o/latest-stable/h2o-docs/flow.html&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;documentation&lt;/a&gt; of how to use H&lt;sub&gt;2&lt;/sub&gt;O flow. But I&amp;rsquo;d like to highlight my favorite features.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;let-s-get-started&#34;&gt;Let&amp;rsquo;s get started&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;First, go to the H&lt;sub&gt;2&lt;/sub&gt;O website to &lt;a href=&#34;http://h2o-release.s3.amazonaws.com/h2o/rel-yates/2/index.html&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;download the zip file&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;download.PNG&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Follow the instruction to unzip the file and run it from your terminal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;cd Downloads
unzip h2o-3.24.0.2.zip
cd h2o-3.24.0.2
java -jar h2o.jar
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Then type &lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:54321&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;http://localhost:54321&lt;/a&gt; in your browser.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;interface.PNG&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;feature-highlight&#34;&gt;Feature highlight&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Notebook layout&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The feature that I appreciate the most is the similar layout as the Jupyter notebook. By adopting the style of the existing tools, it saves the users time from learning using the new interface to really starting to adopt this new tool.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Examples&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Without too much efforts, new users can directly jump into the pipeline by opening the existing projects, i.e., deep learning, GBM, XGbBoost and etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;Control Panel&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;Examples&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;

&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;panel.PNG&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;projects.PNG&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Running time&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another noticable feature of the flow is that users have a better sense of time cost of each component in the pipeline. The running time of each block is shown by default, which also improves the users engagement from using this new tool.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;time.PNG&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Model diagnostics tools&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After the models are implemented and performed, the H&lt;sub&gt;2&lt;/sub&gt;O flow generates a wide range of output for users to select from. Here are some examples from a project using GBM for airline classificaiton.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;Scoring history&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;ROC curve&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;Variable importances&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;

&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;scoring.PNG&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;roc.PNG&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;threshold.PNG&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you would like to know more, here is an article on Medium about democratising machine learning with H&lt;sub&gt;2&lt;/sub&gt;O, which also introduces all the available H&lt;sub&gt;2&lt;/sub&gt;O products including the driverless ai. You can also find a list of publications using H&lt;sub&gt;2&lt;/sub&gt;O &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.h2o.ai/academic/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bayesian modeling with R2jags</title>
      <link>/talk/jags/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2019 18:30:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talk/jags/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to prepare for data scientist interviews with an eCommerce company</title>
      <link>/post/ecommerce/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/ecommerce/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;background&#34;&gt;Background&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I didn&amp;rsquo;t come up with any of those original contents. Here is just a summary of what I&amp;rsquo;ve summarized by learning from reading others&amp;rsquo; insights in how data science contribute to the growth of eCommerce companies and what challenges we are faced with while working as a data scientist at the company.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;5-data-science-projects-every-e-commerce-company-should-do-https-towardsdatascience-com-5-data-science-project-every-e-commerce-company-should-do-8746c5ab4604&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://towardsdatascience.com/5-data-science-project-every-e-commerce-company-should-do-8746c5ab4604&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;5 Data Science Projects Every E-commerce Company Should Do&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this article, the author talked about five important DS projects that should be undergoing at every eCommerce company. I happened to know some of them but didn&amp;rsquo;t realize about the full scope of it. I&amp;rsquo;ll try to elaborate more details about how I&amp;rsquo;ve viewed each topic based on the interview techniques suggested by the Pramp.com (&lt;a href=&#34;https://zhiyang.netlify.com/post/pramp2/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;see my previous article&lt;/a&gt;). I will start with &lt;strong&gt;identifying the goal&lt;/strong&gt; of the company, i.e., the rate of successful booking, followed by &lt;strong&gt;specifying the most informative variables&lt;/strong&gt; to boost that metric, i.e., information from the client and browsing habits, and browsing history. And I proceed with &lt;strong&gt;selecting several models&lt;/strong&gt; to achieve better prediction of the metric.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Recommendation systems&lt;/em&gt;
Companies care very much about the success rates of customers clicking links, adding products into carts and complete purchases. Those can be reflected by the rating or the preference from a user. We can look up information from past searches, previous purchases and information of customers (i.e., location, education level, gender, and etc.). It comes much easier to pick the models for this scenario: collaborative filtering, content based filtering, and hybrid filtering.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Customer lifetime value modeling&lt;/em&gt;
To be honest, I can conceptually understand its important but fail to concretize this idea or even give a mathematical definition of it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Fraud detection&lt;/em&gt;
This is probably the most familiar topic to me because I had some exposure from the machine learning class that I took at USC. It is of course very important and will directly have severe impact the efficiency. Of course, the outcome, that we care the most, is whether the purchase made this time is fraud or not. Essentially, there are lots of variables available for us to detect this abnormality, i.e., different locations detected while login-in, unusual purchase category, different shipping/billing addresses, unusual large orders of the same item, international orders and etc. The models, that could potentially useful to be adopted, include simple logistic regression, time series analysis, clustering and classification (logistic regression), matching algorithms. In this case, we can provide a safer environment for customers to increase their retention and increase company revenue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Important reviews&lt;/em&gt;
This topic comes into two perspectives: 1) we&amp;rsquo;ve already have established system to measure the scale of customers&amp;rsquo; satisfaction. 2) we need to use natural language processing skills to extract those information and quantify them. Then, visualization tools like WordClouds could be potentially helfpul and further be used for sentiment analysis. In a long run, we can maximize usrs&amp;rsquo; satisfaction and increase the retention rate, leading to maximizing the revenue and potential social impact.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What I learned from practicing interviews on Pramp.com</title>
      <link>/post/pramp/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/pramp/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I came across this website to prepare for people to ace interviews for data scientist jobs in the industry. It was mentioned and recommended in the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/pulse/so-you-want-job-data-scientist-daniel-miller/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;post&lt;/a&gt; written by Daniel Miller, a data scientist at Microsoft. I was a little suspicious at the first beginning because I don&amp;rsquo;t think there will be any free services in helping people with improving their interview skills. Normally, we get help from the school Careers Center. I do benefit a lot from visiting the Careers Center at the USC but they could only &lt;strong&gt;go this far to help with resume critique and behavioral questions&lt;/strong&gt;. Anything technical or related to a specific position are beyond what they can offer. So, I am stuck!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Until I gave a try on this website, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.pramp.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Pramp&lt;/a&gt;, it totally changed my perspectives on how to prepare a data scientist interview. Actually, early this year, I was invited by the recruiter to interview for a data scientist position at Google. The phone interview went well and I was invited for an on-site interview. I postponed the interview to early 2019 so I could prepare for it during the winter break. I spent most of my time practicing code and learning more new machine learning models. Later on, I realized that I was totally wrong through the entire process to ace a data scientist interview. None of my preparation touches the surface on how to evaluate a new feature to boost a company’s growth, i.e., how to increase the number of complete successful purchases or boost the growth of users. Obviously, the interview didn’t go well and even I knew it right away after four rounds of the interviews. After a week or two, the recruiter called me and told me that they’ve decided not to move on with my application. I was frustrated and still don’t know how to improve my situation. It’s totally changed after I went on practicing an interview on Pramp.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1600/1*T9rTWkhfFE47aiBtG5vjXA.jpeg&#34; alt=&#34;Screenshot&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The entire process was very simple. During an hour session, two of the participants have the opportunities to play as interviewer and interviewee. I was given a case for a data scientist at Airbnb to ask how the applicant is going to do to improve the growth of successful online booking. My partner did well, actually, better. He did an awesome job in figuring all the questions being asked and almost hit the perfect answer for all of them. In contrast, I did bad and was not even saying things during the interview. It turned out I had hard time with concretizing the business questions to specific metrics to measure the success. What they would like to achieve at the end of the day? What data do we have and challenging would we be faced with in terms of getting the data ready for the next step? Sometimes, it was about what data could be available and possibly collected for this business questions. I’ve learned a lot during the interview and am excited for the next try!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you will be interested in trying out this awesome website to enhance your interview skills, please check out here, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.pramp.com/invt/9XKJnyqA6vSm4Wnbpyqz&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Pramp&lt;/a&gt;. They’ve provided six tracks including applied data science, project manager, behavioral questions, and etc.. You can also read more about them on &lt;a href=&#34;https://blog.pramp.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Medium&lt;/a&gt;. Hope this will help you to land your dream job soon!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HiLDA - a statistical approach to investigate differences in mutational signatures</title>
      <link>/publication/hilda/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/hilda/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to make xaringan slides in R</title>
      <link>/talk/ocrug/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 18:30:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talk/ocrug/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What I&#39;ve learned from rstudio::2019</title>
      <link>/talk/laerug/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 18:30:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talk/laerug/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;talk.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Display Jupyter Notebooks with Academic</title>
      <link>/post/jupyter/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/jupyter/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-python&#34;&gt;from IPython.core.display import Image
Image(&#39;https://www.python.org/static/community_logos/python-logo-master-v3-TM-flattened.png&#39;)
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;./academic_0_0.png&#34; alt=&#34;png&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-python&#34;&gt;print(&amp;quot;Welcome to Academic!&amp;quot;)
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;Welcome to Academic!
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;install-python-and-jupyter&#34;&gt;Install Python and Jupyter&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.anaconda.com/distribution/#download-section&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Install Anaconda&lt;/a&gt; which includes Python 3 and Jupyter notebook.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Otherwise, for advanced users, install Jupyter notebook with &lt;code&gt;pip3 install jupyter&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;create-a-new-blog-post-as-usual-https-sourcethemes-com-academic-docs-managing-content-create-a-blog-post&#34;&gt;Create a new blog post &lt;a href=&#34;https://sourcethemes.com/academic/docs/managing-content/#create-a-blog-post&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;as usual&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Run the following commands in your Terminal, substituting &lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;MY_WEBSITE_FOLDER&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;my-post&lt;/code&gt; with the file path to your Academic website folder and a name for your blog post (without spaces), respectively:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-bash&#34;&gt;cd &amp;lt;MY_WEBSITE_FOLDER&amp;gt;
hugo new  --kind post post/my-post
cd &amp;lt;MY_WEBSITE_FOLDER&amp;gt;/content/post/my-post/
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;create-or-upload-a-jupyter-notebook&#34;&gt;Create or upload a Jupyter notebook&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Run the following command to start Jupyter within your new blog post folder. Then create a new Jupyter notebook (&lt;em&gt;New &amp;gt; Python Notebook&lt;/em&gt;) or upload a notebook.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-bash&#34;&gt;jupyter notebook
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;convert-notebook-to-markdown&#34;&gt;Convert notebook to Markdown&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-bash&#34;&gt;jupyter nbconvert Untitled.ipynb --to markdown --NbConvertApp.output_files_dir=.

# Copy the contents of Untitled.md and append it to index.md:
cat Untitled.md | tee -a index.md

# Remove the temporary file:
rm Untitled.md
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;edit-your-post-metadata&#34;&gt;Edit your post metadata&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Open &lt;code&gt;index.md&lt;/code&gt; in your text editor and edit the title etc. in the &lt;a href=&#34;https://sourcethemes.com/academic/docs/front-matter/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;front matter&lt;/a&gt; according to your preference.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To set a &lt;a href=&#34;https://sourcethemes.com/academic/docs/managing-content/#featured-image&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;featured image&lt;/a&gt;, place an image named &lt;code&gt;featured&lt;/code&gt; into your post&amp;rsquo;s folder.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For other tips, such as using math, see the guide on &lt;a href=&#34;https://sourcethemes.com/academic/docs/writing-markdown-latex/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;writing content with Academic&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn how to make a header with R hex-stickers for LinkedIn and Twitter</title>
      <link>/post/hexwall/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/hexwall/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;background&#34;&gt;Background&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nowadays, peoples use LinkedIn and Twitter to look for opportunities and network with others. Except for gaining more skills and doing projects to boost your profile, there is another way to make your profile more professional: finding the right header. No one will argue with the fact that the header picture helps with creating the first impression for recruiters and your future employers. To begin with creating a profile, it might take forever for you to pick their favorite picture as the header but still keep professional. Here is how to create your own unique header showing your professional skills! If you are an R user, here might be a good idea to create your own header with all your favorite R hex-stickers that is perfect and ready for LinkedIn and Twitter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last year, I came across this post, &lt;a href=&#34;https://blog.mitchelloharawild.com/blog/user-2018-feature-wall/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;USER!2018 Feature Wall&lt;/a&gt;,  by Mitchell O&amp;rsquo;Hara-Wild. I was amazed about the design and aesthetics of this map. In the post, he described his experience of creating a feature wall for the useR!2018 and he wrote a package to do it as well. Today, we will use his codes to make our own header.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://blog.mitchelloharawild.com/blog/2018-07-11-user-2018-feature-wall_files/final.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Screenshot&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;let-s-get-started&#34;&gt;Let&amp;rsquo;s get started&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;First, go to the GitHub repository &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/mitchelloharawild/hexwall&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;mitchelloharawild/hexwall&lt;/a&gt; and follow his instructions to set everything up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Creat your own list of R stickers. Mitchell has recommended downloading from the RStudio hex-stickers from their GitHub repository (&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/rstudio/hex-stickers&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;rstudio/hex-stickers&lt;/a&gt;). Mitchell has provided a folder with some sample stickers. Add more your favorite stickers into that folder.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you prefer some stickers at a particular position, i.e., RStudio hex sticker comes as the first one. Then, you should rename those files to make sure they appear in the right order. Here is a quick peek into my stickers list folder.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;list.PNG&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;By run the following two lines of code, you will get a perfect and professional R stickers wall header for your LinkedIn and Twitter profile.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;source(&#39;hexwall.R&#39;)
hexwall(&amp;quot;samplelist&amp;quot;, sticker_row_size = 7, sticker_width = 200)
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;featured.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Good practices in R</title>
      <link>/talk/rladies/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2019 18:30:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talk/rladies/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Example Page</title>
      <link>/tutorial/example/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2018 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tutorial/example/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;In this tutorial, I&amp;rsquo;ll share my top 10 tips for getting started with Academic:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;tip-1&#34;&gt;Tip 1&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;tip-2&#34;&gt;Tip 2&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Statistical approach for investigating change in mutational processes during cancer growth and development</title>
      <link>/talk/jsmtalk/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 14:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talk/jsmtalk/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;photo.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2018 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/privacy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
