<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>R on Zhi Yang</title>
    <link>/tags/r/</link>
    <description>Recent content in R on Zhi Yang</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2019 14:00:00 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/r/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>R you ready to see awesome R Markdown?</title>
      <link>/talk/rmarkdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2019 14:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talk/rmarkdown/</guid>
      <description>  Nice turnout for the kickstart of the #uscrbootcamp with @malco_barrett, @brookemariebell, and @zhiiiyang spearheading day 1 of track 1! #rstats pic.twitter.com/4qPcsKzxW6 — George G. Vega Yon (@gvegayon) August 19, 2019   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Extracting topics from cancer patients&#39; mutational profiles</title>
      <link>/talk/lda_mutations/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2019 18:30:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talk/lda_mutations/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An interactive treemap of media franchise revenue by category</title>
      <link>/post/treemap/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/treemap/</guid>
      <description>Background Hi, you are probably directed here because of my recent tweet. To practice my data visualization skills, I decided to enter the this week’s #TidyTuesday challenge, which is about how different media franchises stack up with their revenue streams. You can read more about the dataset here.
#TidyTuesday I made an interactive treemap for revenue by category using treemap and d3treeR. #rstats pic.twitter.com/plRYgXSNs2 — Zhi Yang (@zhiiiyang) July 3, 2019    Data visualization library(dplyr) library(ggplot2) library(d3treeR) library(treemap) library(RColorBrewer) library(stringr) dat &amp;lt;- read.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How difficult it is to get into the top universities in China</title>
      <link>/post/gaokao/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/gaokao/</guid>
      <description>Background In June of 2019, over 10 millions students took the gaokao, the college entrace exam in China. This exam varies by province to province, so it is the admission rate to the top universities (Beijing/Tsinghua University). I often get asked how difficult to get into those two schools in China. I hope this data visualization will help you understand the admission rates of the top universities across different provinces in China by using the data in 2017.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yes! I tried the new poster style at a conference</title>
      <link>/post/poster/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/poster/</guid>
      <description>Background I worked for Jessica Barrington-Trimis (@Doctor_BT) on a project to look into the effect of e-cigarette use on cigarette use among adolescents. After we submitted the manuscript, Jessica suggested me presenting the results at the upcoming 2019 Meeting – College on Problems of Drug Dependence, San Antonio, TX. Meanwhile, she sent me a video link about transforming the current poster style. After watching it, I was totally down to get the new poster rolling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E-cigarette product characteristics</title>
      <link>/talk/cpdd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2019 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talk/cpdd/</guid>
      <description> Excited to present the research work with @Doctor_BT at #CPDD19 on the effect of e-cigarette use on past 30-day cigarette use among adolescents. Thank you all for dropping by and asking amazing questions. Also, I’d to share my experience of adopting #betterposter by @mikemorrison pic.twitter.com/N4zt7y6Kh9 — Zhi Yang (@zhiiiyang) June 17, 2019   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Extracting topics from cancer patients&#39; mutational profiles</title>
      <link>/talk/ml4all/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 14:30:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talk/ml4all/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bayesian modeling with R2jags</title>
      <link>/talk/jags/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2019 18:30:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talk/jags/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What I learned from practicing interviews on Pramp.com</title>
      <link>/post/pramp/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/pramp/</guid>
      <description>I came across this website to prepare for people to ace interviews for data scientist jobs in the industry. It was mentioned and recommended in the post written by Daniel Miller, a data scientist at Microsoft. I was a little suspicious at the first beginning because I don&amp;rsquo;t think there will be any free services in helping people with improving their interview skills. Normally, we get help from the school Careers Center.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HiLDA - a statistical approach to investigate differences in mutational signatures</title>
      <link>/publication/hilda/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/hilda/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to make xaringan slides in R</title>
      <link>/talk/xaringan/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 18:30:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talk/xaringan/</guid>
      <description>knitr::include_url(&amp;quot;https://zhiiiyang.github.io/XaringanTutorial/#1)  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What I&#39;ve learned from rstudio::2019</title>
      <link>/talk/laerug/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 18:30:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talk/laerug/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn how to make a header with R hex-stickers for LinkedIn and Twitter</title>
      <link>/post/hexwall/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/hexwall/</guid>
      <description>Background Nowadays, peoples use LinkedIn and Twitter to look for opportunities and network with others. Except for gaining more skills and doing projects to boost your profile, there is another way to make your profile more professional: finding the right header. No one will argue with the fact that the header picture helps with creating the first impression for recruiters and your future employers. To begin with creating a profile, it might take forever for you to pick their favorite picture as the header but still keep professional.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Good practices in R</title>
      <link>/talk/rladies/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2019 18:30:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talk/rladies/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Statistical approach for investigating change in mutational processes during cancer growth and development</title>
      <link>/talk/jsmtalk/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 14:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talk/jsmtalk/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data visualization</title>
      <link>/project/viz/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/viz/</guid>
      <description>This project contains a list of data visualization generated using R.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E-cig use among youth</title>
      <link>/project/ecig/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/ecig/</guid>
      <description>This project is focused on studying e-cigarette Product Characteristics and Frequency of Smoking Among Young Adults. Previous research suggests that e-cigarette use is associated with cigarette initiation, including the frequency and heaviness of cigarette smoking. The goal of this research is to examine the impact of specific e-cigarette characteristics on cigarette smoking frequency. What we did is to use advanced counts model to model the association between the e-cigarette exposures and the outcome, the number of cigarette use in the past 30 days.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Colorectal cancer study</title>
      <link>/project/cancer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/cancer/</guid>
      <description>During my doctoral training, most of my research is focused on developing novel statistical methods for genomics data, specifically, cancer development and tumor growth. This project has enlighted me to work on several interesting perspectives of it, including hierarchical topics model, clustering, and interactive interface. Thanks to my advisors Kimberly Siegmund, and committe member Paul Marjoram and Darryl Shibata.
Motivations Topic models have been widely applied to extract topics from various range of documents or collections of texts, i.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>