<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>R on Zhi Yang</title>
    <link>/tags/r/</link>
    <description>Recent content in R on Zhi Yang</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/r/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>SoCal All Hands useR Meeting Twitter Blog</title>
      <link>/post/socalr2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/socalr2019/</guid>
      <description>Please check out all the slides hereWorkshops by Malcolm Barrett and Emil Hvitfeldt@malco_barrett recommends these three books for you to continue on your #dataviz #ggplot2 learning journey. 📕Fundamentals of Data Visualization by @ClausWilke 📘Storytelling with Data by @storywithdata
📗Better Presentations by @jschwabish pic.twitter.com/10Cdy779SB
&amp;mdash; Los Angeles R Users (@la_Rusers) November 23, 2019  We had a great day at the SoCal #rstats meetup! My workshop from this morning on designing ggplots is freely available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How R Markdown helped me thrive in scientific research and advance my career development?</title>
      <link>/talk/uscbiostat/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2019 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talk/uscbiostat/</guid>
      <description>Happy Scientist Seminar for the Department of Preventive Medicine at USC</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yes! I tried the new poster style at a conference</title>
      <link>/post/poster/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/poster/</guid>
      <description>my first-time experience of making a trending new-style poster</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How R Markdown family automates the last mile of analytics</title>
      <link>/talk/sbrug/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2019 17:30:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talk/sbrug/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;#39;re visiting our #rstats friends up in Santa Barbara! @zhiiiyang giving a talk on how R Markdown can automate the last mile of your work @RLadiesSB pic.twitter.com/WXzS7hhWv7
&amp;mdash; Los Angeles R Users (@la_Rusers) September 19, 2019  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bioconductor R package</title>
      <link>/project/hilda/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2019 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/hilda/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mutational signature app</title>
      <link>/project/shiny/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2019 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/shiny/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>R you ready to see awesome R Markdown?</title>
      <link>/talk/rmarkdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2019 14:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talk/rmarkdown/</guid>
      <description>A introduction to the family of R Markdown packages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Extracting topics from cancer patients&#39; mutational profiles</title>
      <link>/talk/lda_mutations/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2019 18:30:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talk/lda_mutations/</guid>
      <description>An application of topic modeling in genomic data</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An interactive treemap of media franchise revenue by category</title>
      <link>/post/treemap/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/treemap/</guid>
      <description>An interactive treemap using treemap and d3treeR</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How difficult it is to get into the top universities in China</title>
      <link>/post/gaokao/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/gaokao/</guid>
      <description>data visualization of the college entrace exam data in 2017</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E-cigarette product characteristics</title>
      <link>/talk/cpdd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2019 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talk/cpdd/</guid>
      <description>Young adults using mod (vs. pen-like) e-cigarette devices at baseline smoked &lt;strong&gt;more than 6 times&lt;/strong&gt; as many cigarettes in the past 30 days at follow-up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Extracting topics from cancer patients&#39; mutational profiles</title>
      <link>/talk/ml4all/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 14:30:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talk/ml4all/</guid>
      <description>An introduction on how to apply topic modeling on somatic mutations</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bayesian modeling with R2jags</title>
      <link>/talk/jags/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2019 18:30:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talk/jags/</guid>
      <description>a gentle introduction on how to fit a simple Bayesian model, visualize and summarize the output using R2jags.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What I learned from practicing interviews on Pramp.com</title>
      <link>/post/pramp/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/pramp/</guid>
      <description>What I&amp;rsquo;ve learned from practicing interviews on Pramp for the first time</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HiLDA - a statistical approach to investigate differences in mutational signatures</title>
      <link>/publication/hilda/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/hilda/</guid>
      <description>We propose a hierarchical latent Dirichlet allocation model (HiLDA) for characterizing somatic mutation data in cancer. The method allows us to infer mutational patterns and their relative frequencies in a set of tumor mutational catalogs and to compare the estimated frequencies between tumor sets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to make xaringan slides in R</title>
      <link>/talk/xaringan/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 18:30:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talk/xaringan/</guid>
      <description>A tutorial talk on how to make xaringan slides in R</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What I&#39;ve learned from rstudio::2019</title>
      <link>/talk/laerug/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 18:30:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talk/laerug/</guid>
      <description>A talk on what I&amp;rsquo;ve learned from going to the RStudio conference 2019</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn how to make a header with R hex-stickers for LinkedIn and Twitter</title>
      <link>/post/hexwall/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/hexwall/</guid>
      <description>Learn how to make a header with R hex-stickers for LinkedIn and Twitter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Good practices in R</title>
      <link>/talk/rladies/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2019 18:30:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talk/rladies/</guid>
      <description>An example talk on developing good pratices in R</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Statistical approach for investigating change in mutational processes during cancer growth and development</title>
      <link>/talk/jsmtalk/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 14:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talk/jsmtalk/</guid>
      <description>An example talk using Academic&amp;rsquo;s Markdown slides feature.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data visualization</title>
      <link>/project/viz/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/viz/</guid>
      <description>This project contains a list of data visualization generated using R.
Tweets#TidyTuesday I made an interactive treemap for revenue by category using treemap and d3treeR. #rstats pic.twitter.com/plRYgXSNs2
&amp;mdash; Zhi Yang, PhD 🎄❄️ (@zhiiiyang) July 3, 2019  The gaokao is the national college entrance exam taken by Chinese students in June. In 2019, over 10M students took the exam. I hope this viz could help you understand how difficult to get into the top universities (Beijing and Tsinghua University) in China.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E-cig use among youth</title>
      <link>/project/ecig/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/ecig/</guid>
      <description>This project is focused on studying e-cigarette Product Characteristics and Frequency of Smoking Among Young Adults. Previous research suggests that e-cigarette use is associated with cigarette initiation, including the frequency and heaviness of cigarette smoking. The goal of this research is to examine the impact of specific e-cigarette characteristics on cigarette smoking frequency. What we did is to use advanced counts model to model the association between the e-cigarette exposures and the outcome, the number of cigarette use in the past 30 days.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Colorectal cancer study</title>
      <link>/project/cancer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/cancer/</guid>
      <description>During my doctoral training, most of my research is focused on developing novel statistical methods for genomics data, specifically, cancer development and tumor growth. This project has enlighted me to work on several interesting perspectives of it, including hierarchical topics model, clustering, and interactive interface. Thanks to my advisors Kimberly Siegmund, and committe member Paul Marjoram and Darryl Shibata.
MotivationsTopic models have been widely applied to extract topics from various range of documents or collections of texts, i.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>