<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>R, Data Science on Zhi Yang</title>
    <link>/tags/r-data-science/</link>
    <description>Recent content in R, Data Science on Zhi Yang</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/r-data-science/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How to prepare for data scientist interviews with an eCommerce company</title>
      <link>/post/ecommerce/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/ecommerce/</guid>
      <description>Background I didn&amp;rsquo;t come up with any of those original contents. Here is just a summary of what I&amp;rsquo;ve summarized by learning from reading others&amp;rsquo; insights in how data science contribute to the growth of eCommerce companies and what challenges we are faced with while working as a data scientist at the company.
5 Data Science Projects Every E-commerce Company Should Do In this article, the author talked about five important DS projects that should be undergoing at every eCommerce company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What I learned from practicing interviews on Pramp.com</title>
      <link>/post/pramp/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/pramp/</guid>
      <description>I came across this website to prepare for people to ace interviews for data scientist jobs in the industry. It was mentioned and recommended in the post written by Daniel Miller, a data scientist at Microsoft. I was a little suspicious at the first beginning because I don&amp;rsquo;t think there will be any free services in helping people with improving their interview skills. Normally, we get help from the school Careers Center.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>