<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Zhi Yang</title>
    <link>/project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Zhi Yang</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 00:00:00 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Data visualization</title>
      <link>/project/viz/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/viz/</guid>
      <description>This project contains a list of data visualization generated using R.
Tweets#TidyTuesday I made an interactive treemap for revenue by category using treemap and d3treeR. #rstats pic.twitter.com/plRYgXSNs2
&amp;mdash; Zhi Yang (@zhiiiyang) July 3, 2019  The gaokao is the national college entrance exam taken by Chinese students in June. In 2019, over 10M students took the exam. I hope this viz could help you understand how difficult to get into the top universities (Beijing and Tsinghua University) in China.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E-cig use among youth</title>
      <link>/project/ecig/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/ecig/</guid>
      <description>This project is focused on studying e-cigarette Product Characteristics and Frequency of Smoking Among Young Adults. Previous research suggests that e-cigarette use is associated with cigarette initiation, including the frequency and heaviness of cigarette smoking. The goal of this research is to examine the impact of specific e-cigarette characteristics on cigarette smoking frequency. What we did is to use advanced counts model to model the association between the e-cigarette exposures and the outcome, the number of cigarette use in the past 30 days.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Colorectal cancer study</title>
      <link>/project/cancer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/cancer/</guid>
      <description>During my doctoral training, most of my research is focused on developing novel statistical methods for genomics data, specifically, cancer development and tumor growth. This project has enlighted me to work on several interesting perspectives of it, including hierarchical topics model, clustering, and interactive interface. Thanks to my advisors Kimberly Siegmund, and committe member Paul Marjoram and Darryl Shibata.
MotivationsTopic models have been widely applied to extract topics from various range of documents or collections of texts, i.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>